

#### **Profile**

I am a passionate mobile app developer with a strong desire to continue learning and improving my skills.

I have experience developing both native and hybrid apps.

I am highly motivated, detail-oriented, and enjoy working collaboratively with teams.

### Contact

: Naples, Italy **:** +39 3669592792

: bryansanchez.311@gmail.com

My portfolio





# **Professional Experiences**

#### Capgemini (Mobile Developer) 2024 - Present

In Capgemini, I contributed to the development of the Bancomat app, integrating services such as Firebase Cloud Messaging and Remote Config. I developed brand new internal products. These experiences allowed me to improve my Flutter skills exploring the Clean Architecture, BLOC and animations.

### Alfa Group (Mobile Developer) 2023 - 2024

First company experience as mobile developer.

Implemented iOS-style design, integration tests and Firebase Cloud Messaging notifications.

Developed closed-source Swift Packages.

Learned Google Cloud fundamentals.

# Additional Experiences

#### S-Park

I created and developed S-Park, a multi-platform app available on both the App Store and Play Store. During development, I deepened my knowledge of Dart, Flutter and Firebase.

# **Education and Training**

#### Apple Developer Academy 2022-2023

I attended the Apple Developer Academy after passing two admission exams, where I developed iOS applications using Swift and learned to communicate with professionals from different areas of app development.

I enriched my portfolio and deepened my knowledge of Git, FileMaker, SwiftUI, UIKit, and other iOS frameworks such as CallKit, HomeKit, WidgetKit, and WeatherKit. Additionally, I improved my presentation skills by developing and presenting each application to internal and external stakeholders.

#### Google Project Management Certificate, 2022-2023

I completed Google Certificates' courses to gain experience as a project manager through real-world scenarios, from the planning to the closure of projects. During the courses I learned the theory and use of Waterfall and Agile methodologies and create effective project documents, charts and presentations. I also practiced in soft skill such as negotiation, influencing, coaching, strategic thinking, problem solving, communication and more. For manage project, I used many software tools such as Asana, Google Docs, Google Sheets, Google Presentations.

### Cisco Networking Academy 2021-2022

In Cisco I learned how to design, build, and maintain computer networks, as well as how to troubleshoot common network issues. Additionally, I gained a strong understanding of network security and how to implement security measures to protect against cyber threats.

Through hands-on labs and simulations, utilizing tools such as Packet Tracer, I developed practical experience working with Cisco networking equipment and became proficient in using networking protocols and technologies such as TCP/IP, VLANs, and routing protocols.

### High School Degree: Computer Science 98/100 (IIS Carlo Levi - Portici) 2017-2022

During my studies in high school. I learned the basics of software/web development, database management, and network systems. I finished school with a knowledge of programming (C++, Java, CSS, HTML, JavaScript, Arduino, Assembly, MySQL), computer programs (Oracle, XAMPP, DEVC++, NetBeans, MySQL Workbench) and project management (Waterfall).

### **Technical Skills:**

- IOS Development
- Android Development Multi-platform Development (Flutter)
- UI Frameworks (SwiftUI, UIKit, Flutter, Native Android)
- Design Patterns (MVVM, MVC, MVP, Clean)
- Git
- Firebase
- Google Cloud
- FileMaker Code Linters
- Project Management (Waterfall and Agile)

### Soft skills:

- leamwork
- Public speaking Presentation
- · Working under pressure
- Negotiation
- Task estimation
- Coaching
- · Problem solving
- Stakeholder management
- Working in international environment
- · English and Italian language

## Certificates

- Apple Developer Academy
- Google Certificates Project Management
- Cisco Networking Academy
- iOS App Development course from Udemy, Inc.
- Android App Development course from Udemy, Inc.
- Flutter Development course from Udemy, Inc.
- New ECDL
- Huawei ICT Academy